gpotato.com 2014-05-19

# gPotato Game Portal - Enjoy Free-to-Play Online Games!

## WEBZEN West Inc. (Effective Date: July, 2007)

WEBZEN West Inc. (“WEBZEN West Inc.”) maintains this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) that summarizes our policies and processes for protecting the privacy of all personal information gathered from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our website(s) or who download WEBZEN West Inc.'s products and services, and when and how such information is collected, used, and safeguarded. This Policy also explains how anyone can review, update, correct, or delete their personal information and specify what information, if any, they would like to receive from WEBZEN West Inc. on an on-going basis.

### Introduction

WEBZEN West Inc. is committed to ensuring your privacy and protecting the security of your personal information. This Policy covers the public WEBZEN West Inc. websites - [http://www.gpotato.com](http://www.gpotato.com/), [http://billing.gpotato.com](http://billing.gpotato.com/), [http://flyff.gpotato.com](http://flyff.gpotato.com/), [http://rappelz.gpotato.com](http://rappelz.gpotato.com/) and [http://allods.gpotato.com](http://allods.gpotato.com/) sites (collectively, the “Website”) — and all online forms on the Website used to collect personal information. Please note that this Policy applies only to sites maintained by WEBZEN West Inc. or its affiliates, and not third party sites, whether linked to or from the Website. Moreover, this Policy does not only apply to information collected by WEBZEN West Inc. offline. In addition, this Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. By using the Website, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of this Policy and that your use of the Website, including, downloads of any of WEBZEN West Inc.'s products and services, is subject to WEBZEN West Inc.'s Terms of Service. **If you do not agree with any terms or conditions described in this Policy or the Terms of Service, please exit from the Website.**

### Collecting Personal Information

You can access our Website without providing us with any personal information. However, WEBZEN West Inc. may collect personal information in various locations on our Website as more particularly described below. Our primary goal in collecting the information described below is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Website and to deliver better service, products, and more relevant content to our customers, prospective customers, and visitors.

### Personal Information We Collect

Personal information may be collected from you during (a) the registration process, (b) promotional campaigns, (c) customer support and technical service requests, and/or (d) ordering of products and other services from the Website or from third party service providers. This information may include, but is not limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, birth date, occupation, gender, account ID, passwords, and/or payment and billing information. From time to time we may expand or change the information requested upon registration, so this may not be a complete list. We ask that you provide only your own personal information, not personal information concerning anyone else. Personal information may be collected by WEBZEN West Inc. and/or business partners such as co-sponsors.

Top

### Cookies

A “cookie” is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We may use cookies to track general, non-personal information about our users (e.g., user name, pages viewed, time spent our Website, and the websites visited just before and just after our Website) for statistical and market research purposes. The information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis.

We use cookies to gather information about our Website users' browser activities in order to constantly improve our Website and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in a most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Website to better meet the needs of our customers, prospective customers, and visitors.

You have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the option to reject all cookies, which may, however, in limited instances prevent you from accessing certain features on our Website.

### Log Files

Like most Internet services, we may also use log files on the server side. The data held in log files includes your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, e-mail application, Internet service provider, referring/exit Web pages, computer platform type, date/time stamp, and user activity (e.g., feature usage, user rankings, game statistics). WEBZEN West Inc. uses server log data to analyze trends, administer the services offered through the Website. IP addresses are not tied to any personally identifiable information.

The software enabling the Website has associated log and temporary files that are stored on WEBZEN West Inc.'s servers. These files store your account information, preference settings, system notifications as well as other data necessary to enable you to participate on the Website. Your information may also exist within regularly performed server backups.

The foregoing information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis. 

### Monitoring/Public Information

When any game is updated or “patched”, our patch routine may check your computer to see that you have the most recent version of game-specific files; when you communicate within any game or any other communication feature within the game (e.g., live chat, instant message services and the like), even “privately” to another person, you do so with the understanding that those communications go through our servers, can be monitored by us, you have no expectation of privacy in any of those communications and, accordingly, you expressly consent to monitoring of communications that you send and receive.

You may also choose to disclose personal information in our online chat rooms, blogs, bulletin boards, and other public forums made available through the Website. Personal information you disclose in such public forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality. Please refer to the Terms of Service for additional information relating to the disclosure of personal information on public forums.

Top

### Monitoring/Public Information

When any game is updated or “patched”, our patch routine may check your computer to see that you have the most recent version of game-specific files; when you communicate within any game or any other communication feature within the game (e.g., live chat, instant message services and the like), even “privately” to another person, you do so with the understanding that those communications go through our servers, can be monitored by us, you have no expectation of privacy in any of those communications and, accordingly, you expressly consent to monitoring of communications that you send and receive.

You may also choose to disclose personal information in our online chat rooms, blogs, bulletin boards, and other public forums made available through the Website. Personal information you disclose in such public forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality. Please refer to the Terms of Service for additional information relating to the disclosure of personal information on public forums.

### Human Resources

Some of the pages associated with our Website may relate to employment opportunities or human resources. They usually will be captioned “Career” or “Current Opening Positions” or will have similar labels or captions clearly indicating the employment opportunity subject matter (the “Career Pages”) and such pages may be co-branded with third party service providers. Any personal information that you submit through Careers Pages will be collected in the United States and will be reviewed by our employees or consultants to evaluate your qualifications and experience for job opportunities in the United States. Your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties other than third parties who provide services to us. We will (and each of our third party service providers with access to such information will agree with us they will) take any legally required steps to secure your personal information. We will use your personal information for recruitment purposes, and if you are offered a job or become employed by us, for other employment-related purposes. By submitting information through Careers Pages, you agree that we may use the information for recruitment and employment purposes (including transferring the data to other countries, transferring your information to other companies authorized to perform specific services, and/or other processing relevant to recruitment purposes).

Resumes should include information relevant to your employment history and education (degrees obtained, places worked, positions held, relevant awards, and so forth). We recommend that you do not disclose sensitive personal characteristics (e.g., gender, height, weight, religion, philosophical or political beliefs, sexual orientation, financial data, marital status, etc.) in your initial resume or letters. Please note that your information will be processed and/or stored in U.S. databases. By submitting your resume, you are consenting to the export of your information to the U.S. for processing and storage.

Except where you instruct us to remove your resume, we will keep the information for other consideration. If you need to update or otherwise make changes to you resume, simply resubmit a new resume. If you wish to have your resume completely removed from our systems, please follow the procedures described in the Opt-Out Provision below. 

### Use of Personal Information

Unless otherwise described elsewhere in this Policy, we will not disclose any personal information collected from customers, prospective customers, or visitors.

Top

### Use by WEBZEN West Inc.

We use the information you provide so that we may better understand the needs of our customers, prospective customers, and visitors. Specifically, we use your personal information for many purposes, including: 

  * to allow you to register to use our products and services; 
  * to apply for employment opportunities at WEBZEN West Inc.;
  * to ensure the continued smooth operation of our service;
  * to analyze user characteristics and usage patterns in order to better understand how our products and service are used and market them more effectively;
  * to communicate with you concerning your account or to send you newsletters, surveys, contest and sweepstake announcements, and information about our service or product offerings or the offerings of our business partners;
  * to prevent or investigate actual or suspected fraud, hacking, infringement, or other misconduct involving our products and services, or this Website;
  * to respond to inquiries, troubleshoot problems, investigate incidents, and handle complaints; and
  * to develop to new products and services.

### Sharing with Business Partners

We do not sell or trade any personal information about our customers, prospects, or visitors to any third parties. We may share, however, aggregated demographic information with our business partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We may also periodically engage in co-marketing activities, where we work with a complementary solution provider to launch a joint marketing program. In these situations, we will only send information to you on behalf of the other; we do not provide your personal information to such partner. We may also enter into business partnerships with other parties to provide specific services. If a user signs up for these services or responds to a particular marketing offer, we may share personal information such as your name or other contact information that is necessary for our business partner to provide these services or get in contact with you.

Finally, in the event WEBZEN West Inc. combines with another company in the future through a corporate merger, sale, acquisition, liquidation or other similar process, your personal information may be transferred with the business or a part of it, or may be sold as an asset of the business.

### Storage of Personal Information and Security

We take reasonable precaution to protect the personal information we collect from customers, prospective customers, and visitors. When users submit personal information via the Website, the information is housed in a secure in-house database. To prevent unauthorized access, loss, or misuse, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information we maintain. WEBZEN West Inc. uses industry-standard technology, such as firewalls, in an effort to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. Moreover, we encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us (e.g., account passwords and payment-related identifiable information) via SSL (secured socket layer) protocol in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity.

In addition, only employees who need the information to perform their duties are granted access to personally identifiable information. The unauthorized access or use of such information by an employee is prohibited and constitutes grounds for disciplinary action. Additionally, our information management systems are configured in such a way as to block or inhibit employees from accessing information that they have no authority to access.

Furthermore, our trusted vendors and business partners are responsible for processing or handling some of the information that we receive. These vendors and business partners are not authorized to use such information for purposes beyond those specified by us and are required to preserve the confidentiality with which we treat such information.

However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you should know that information sent over the Internet, whether by e-mail or by using one of our on-line forms, is not necessarily secure against interception. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for such interception and cannot guarantee the security of such information.

### Opt-Out Provision

When we first collect information from you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personal information shared with parties outside of WEBZEN West Inc. (unless otherwise described in this Policy). In addition, if you do not want WEBZEN West Inc. to send you e-mail or postal mail about our products and services, you can opt-out at the time of registration or information collection. If, at a later date, you choose to have your name or any other personal information removed from our mailing list, you can do so by emailing [info@gala-net.com](mailto:info@gala-net.com). Alternatively, you may contact us at:

WEBZEN West Inc.  
555 North Mathilda Ave, Suite 220  
Sunnyvale, CA 94085  
Attn: Privacy Policy Request

Top

### California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for use of your personal information by third parties (such as co-sponsors or advertisers) for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

WEBZEN West Inc. qualifies for the alternative option; it has a comprehensive privacy policy and provides you with details on how you may opt-out or opt-in to the use of your personal information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). You may contact us in two ways. Send an email to [info@gala-net.com](mailto:info@gala-net.com). Alternatively, you may contact us at:

WEBZEN West Inc.  
555 North Mathilda Ave, Suite 220  
Sunnyvale, CA 94085  
Attn: Privacy Policy Request

For requests sent via email, you must put the statement “Privacy Policy Request” in the subject field of your email. All requests sent via postal mail must be labeled “Privacy Policy Request” on the envelope or post card and clearly stated on the actual request. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Your street address is optional if you wish to receive a response to your request via email. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping. We will not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

### Review, Update, Correct, or Delete Personal Information

Generally, you may review, update, correct or delete your personal information collected by the Website. You may also correct factual inaccuracies. Certain types of personal information that is necessary to check eligibility, such as birth date or age, cannot be deleted, but may be modified with sufficient verification of the new information. Note that we reserve the right to terminate or delete any registration or promotional entry if we believe the personal information submitted was knowingly false or fraudulent.  
To review, update, correct or delete your personal information collected by the Website, please email [info@gala-net.com](mailto:info@gala-net.com). Alternatively, you may contact us at:

WEBZEN West Inc.  
555 North Mathilda Ave, Suite 220  
Sunnyvale, CA 94085  
Attn: Privacy Policy Request 

To have access to your personal information, you must provide proof of identification such as full name, street address, city/state and zip code, user ID and password, and/or information about your recent activity on the Website. We reserve the right to deny access to any user if we believe there is a question about your identity. And if the burden or expense of providing access to your personal information is disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or if the legitimate rights of others would be violated, we may decide not to provide access to such information. Moreover, we may still retain your information in our files to resolve disputes, enforce the Terms of Service, and for technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the Website. 

Top

### Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose personal information when required by law, regulation, court order, or in response to a subpoena or litigation discovery request, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Policy, we will post those changes on our Policy page so you are aware of what personal information we collect from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our Website, and when and how such information is collected, used and safeguarded. You are responsible for periodically checking our Website for changes to this Policy. If at any time we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain e-mail consent from you. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your personal information in this different manner.

### No Guarantees

While this Policy states our standards for maintenance of personal information and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of personal information. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of any personal information collected from customers, prospective customers, or visitors.

### Links to Third Party Websites

Please be advised that the Website may contain certain hyperlinks to other websites. Although these websites may have privacy policies, all of these websites and their privacy policies are independent of our Website and this Policy. We are not responsible for compliance with other websites' privacy policies or data collection practices. You should review these privacy policies carefully before providing personal information to these websites.

### Protection of Children's Privacy

WEBZEN West Inc. is committed to providing special protection for the privacy of children who may visit the Website. WEBZEN West Inc. is also committed to fully complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We encourage parents to spend time online with their children, become familiar with the features of the Website and participate in the activities offered on the Website. 

Our protections for the privacy of children include the following:

The Website is not directed to children under the age of 13. The Website prohibits registration by, and WEBZEN West Inc. will not knowingly collect, use or retain personally identifiable information from anyone under 13, for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing or promotional purposes). This requirement will be posted at points of data collection within the Website, such as registration for services. In addition, we will delete any records of such personal information that come to our attention.

Since we do not knowingly collect any personal information from visitors to the Website who are under 13, we do not disclose or transfer any such information to third parties.

We do not request any visitor to provide any information about their family members, friends or other persons. 

We do not allow visitors who are under 13 to be listed in any directory of registered users, to participate in any of our chat services, to register for contests, sweepstakes, promotions, or newsletters, or to receive direct marketing from WEBZEN West Inc. or from our third-party affiliates or service or product providers. 

### Special Note to Parents

If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information at the Website, we invite you to notify us so that we may delete the information from our records and discontinue any related features or services (see Opt-Out Provision above). We also urge parents to instruct their children never to give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers without parental permission when using the Internet. We appreciate your cooperation in assisting us to provide a safe and enjoyable online experience for your children. 

### Users Outside United States

WEBZEN West Inc. is a U.S. company and WEBZEN West Inc.'s business operations are primarily conducted in the State of California, U.S.A. We operate our company and administer this Policy under applicable U.S. and California laws and regulations. If you use our service from outside United States, you are thereby consenting for your personal information to be processed in the United States in the manner described in this Policy. Furthermore, you acknowledge that the privacy laws of the United States and the State of California may differ from the laws in the country where you are located and may not provide you the same rights or protections as those laws. 

Top

### Contact Us

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Policy, or have other questions or suggestions about our Website, please contact us via e-mail at
